Guide to the Frederick R. Koch Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Name List
  - Wolf-Ferrari, Ermanno
    - MUSIC
      - Unidentified
        - Piano music, waltz: draft, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.80
        - Piano music, waltzes: draft, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.81
      - Exercises
        - "Auflösungen aus dem Mollakkord": harmonic exercises based on the Tristan chord, 1928 Nov 20
          FRKF 1200.05
        - "Bassschritte": harmonic exercises, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.08
        - Contrapuntal exercises, [early 1890s]
          FRKF 1200.16
        - Embellishments for Rossini's Semiramide, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1398)
          FRKF 1200.49
        - Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, Paride ed Elena. O del mio dolce ardor: copy of the vocal line, n.d.
          Unidentified sketch on verso
        - Rossini, Gioacchino, Il barbiere di Siviglia: harmonic analyses, n.d.
          FRKF 1200.27
    - WRITINGS
      - Dialogue, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1399)
  - Zandonai, Riccardo
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Photograph of Zandonai (Box 61, Folder 1400)
        Inscribed with music quotation from Giulietta e Romeo
        FRKF 1342.3
  - Zemlinsky, Alexander
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 1401)
        FRKF 396
  - Unidentified
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Unidentified, 1900 Aug 16 (Box 61, Folder 1402)
        From an unidentified actor
        FRKF 716d
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Document concerning the Seven Years' War (Box 61, Folder 1403)
- Volumes, flat shelving, oversize, and art
  - Volumes
    - Augenstein, Johann Huldreich
      - Other Papers/Album amicorum, 1640-44, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1404)
    - Boccherini, Luigi
      - Music/ Quintet, piano, strings, G. 413-418, [1799] (Box 63, Folder 1405)
    - Cocteau, Jean
      - Writings/ Les mariés de la Tour Eiffel, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1406)
    - Daudet, Alphonse
      - Writings/ L'Arlésienne: draft and fragments, [ca. 1871-72] (Box 65, Folder 1407)
      - Writings/ L'Arlésienne: incomplete draft, [ca. 1871-72] (Box 66, Folder 1408)
      - Writings/ L'Arlésienne: incomplete draft and fragments, [ca. 1871-72] (Box 67, Folder 1409)
    - Feydeau, Georges
      - Writings/Monologues, 1878-80 (Box 68, Folder 1410)
    - Frederick II, King of Prussia
      - Writings/ Les matinées royales, n.d. (Box 69, Folder 1411)
    - French, Annie
      - Drawings/"While Listening to the Wireless, 1940 (Box 70, Folder 1412)
    - Hahn Reynaldo
      - Writings/Diary, 1897-99 (Box 71, Folder 1413)
      - Writings/Diary concerning Sarah Bernhardt, 1901-02 (Box 72, Folder 1414)
    - Jilek, August
      - Correspondence/Maximilian, Emperor of Mexico (letter case) (Box 73, Folder 1415)
    - Keppel family
      - Other Papers/Original binding (Box 74, Folder 1416)
    - Lear, Edward
      - Writings and Drawings/ A Book of Nonsense /Limericks and drawings, [1835-40?] (Box 75, Folder 1417)
      - Writings and Drawings/ A Book of Nonsense /Limericks and drawings, [early 1840s?] (Box 76, Folder 1418)
      - Writings and Drawings/ A Book of Nonsense /Limericks and drawings, [late 1870s] (Box 77, Folder 1419)
      - Writings and Drawings/Other writings and drawings/"A Walk on a Windy Da+", 1860 Dec 26 (Box 78, Folder 1420)
    - Lecocq, Charles
      - Music/Operas, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 1421)
    - Louise-Marie, of Orléans, Queen
      - Writings/Diary, 1850 May-Sep (Box 80, Folder 1422)
    - Mascagni, Pietro
      - Music/ Alla gioia, 1881-82 (Box 81, Folder 1423)
    - Maugham, Robin
      - Maugham family papers/Other Maugham family/Writings, clippings, and other documents, 1825, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 1424)
    - Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix
      - Other Papers/Album of drawings relating to Mendelssohn-Bartholdy's tour of Scotland in 1829, [1846 or 1847] (Box 83, Folder 1425)
    - Pergolesi, Giovanni Battista
      - Music/ La fenice sul rogo, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 1426)
    - Poulenc, Francis
      - Music/ Les animaux modèles, [1942] (Box 85, Folder 1427)
    - Robert, Louis de
      - Writings/Papa, 1895 (Box 86, Folder 1428)
    - Stravinsky, Igor
      - Music/ Baika, 1916 (Box 87, Folder 1429)
  - Volumes Shelved Flat
    - Balfe, M. W. (Michael William)
      - Music/ Satanella, 1858 Aug 22-24 (Box 88, Folder 1430)
    - Bantock, Granville, Sir
      - Other Papers/Guest book, [ca. 1898]-1947 (Box 89, Folder 1431)
    - Beeching, Frank
      - Drawings/Album of drawings, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 1432)
    - Berlioz, Hector
      - Music/ Roi Lear, 1831 May 7 (Box 91, Folder 1433)
    - Berners, Gerald Hugh Tyrwhitt-Wilson, Baron
      - Music/ The Triumph of Neptune, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 1434)
    - Cocteau, Jean
      - Writings/ Bric-à-brac, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 1435)
      - Writings/"Soignez la gloire de votre firme...", [ca. 1929] (Box 94, Folder 1436)
    - Debussy, Claude
      - Music/ Jeux, [1912] (Box 95, Folder 1437)
      - Music/ Pelléas et Mélisande, 1893-1901 (Box 96, Folder 1438)
    - Dukas, Paul
      - Music/ Vélléda, 1880-81 (Box 97, Folder 1439)
    - Dumas, Alexandre, 1824-1895
      - Other Papers/Album relating to La dame aux camélias, 1843-84, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 1440)
    - Fouquier-Tinville, Antoine Quentin
      - Correspondence/Pommier, Rabau, [1793 Oct 9] (Box 99, Folder 1441)
    - Franck, César
      - Music/ Les béatitudes, 1879 Jul 10 (Box 100, Folder 1442)
    - Genet, Jean
      - Writings/ Les bonnes, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 1443)
    - Gide, André
      - Writings/"Oscar Wilde", [1901] (Box 102, Folder 1444)
    - Giordano, Umberto
      - Music/ Marina, [ca. 1889] (Box 103, Folder 1445)
    - Gounod, Charles
      - Music/ George Dandin, [1873-74] (Box 104, Folder 1446)
      - Music/ Le médecin malgré lui, 1857 (Box 105, Folder 1447)
    - Guitry, Sacha
      - Writings/ Je t'aime, [1919] (Box 106, Folder 1448)
      - Writings/ Un monde fou (Box 107, Folder 1449)
    - Hahn, Reynaldo
      - Music/ Les feuilles blessés, 1897-1906 (Box 108, Folder 1450)
      - Music/Songs and piano music, [1888?]-91, n.d. (Box 109, Folder 1451)
    - Halévy, F.
      - Music/ La tentation, 1832 (Box 110, Folder 1452)
    - Hofmannsthal, Hugo von
      - Writings/ Elektra, n.d. (Box 111, Folder 1453)
      - Writings/"Das Märchen der 672ten Nacht", 1895 Apr (Box 112, Folder 1454)
    - Hugo, Victor
      - Other Papers/Album relating to Victor Hugo, 1821-[70s], n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1455)
    - Ireland, John
      - Music/ The Forgotten Rite, 1913, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 1456)
    - Lear, Edward
      - Writings and Drawings/ A Book of Nonsense /Limericks and drawings, [1835-40?] (Box 115, Folder 1457)
    - Leoncavallo, Ruggiero
      - Music/ La coupe et les lèvres, n.d. (Box 116, Folder 1458)
      - Music/ Maiá: sketches and short score, 1907-08 (Box 117, Folder 1459)
      - Music/ Malbruk: drafts and incomplete short score, [ca. 1909] (Box 118, Folder 1460)
      - Music/ Pierrot au cinéma: drafts and fragments, [ca. 1919] (Box 119, Folder 1461)
      - Music/ La reginetta delle rose, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 1462)
      - Music/ Der Roland von Berlin, 1903, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 1463)
      - Music/ Zazà, n.d. (Box 122, Folder 1464)
      - Music/ Zingari, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 1465)
      - Music/Unidentified/Scores, parts, and fragments, possibly relating to Malbruk (Box 124, Folder 1466)
    - Léopold I, King of the Belgians
      - Other Papers/Appointment of negotiators for marriage treaty, 1816 Mar 9 (Box 125, Folder 1467)
      - Other Papers/Ratification of marriage treaty, 1816 Mar 16 (Box 126, Folder 1468)
    - Liszt, Franz
      - Music/ Ich möchte hingehn, n.d. (Box 127, Folder 1469)
    - Mascagni, Pietro
      - Music/ In filanda, 1880-81 (Box 128, Folder 1470)
      - Music/ Isabeau, n.d. (Box 129, Folder 1471)
      - Music/ Sì, 1919 Sep 10-29 (Box 130, Folder 1472)
    - Massenet, Jules
      - Music/ Amadis, [1910?] (Box 131, Folder 1473)
      - Music/ Bacchus, [1908] (Box 132, Folder 1474)
      - Music/ Cléopâtre, [ca. 1912] (Box 133, Folder 1475)
      - Music/ Les Erinnyes, [1872-76] (Box 134, Folder 1476)
      - Music/ Eve, 1874 Nov 1 (Box 135, Folder 1477)
      - Music/ Fantaisie, violoncello, orchestra, D major, 1896-97 (Box 136, Folder 1478)
      - Music/ Hérodiade, 1879-80 (Box 137, Folder 1479)
      - Music/ Jérusalem, [1912] (Box 138, Folder 1480)
      - Music/ Marche solennelle, 1881 (Box 139, Folder 1481)
      - Music/ Panurge, [ca. 1912] (Box 140, Folder 1482)
      - Music/ Roma, [ca. 1909-10] (Box 141, Folder 1483)
      - Music/ Scènes alsaciennes, 1881 Jul-Aug (Box 142, Folder 1484)
      - Music/ Scènes hongroises, 1871-75 (Box 143, Folder 1485)
      - Music/ Scènes napolitaines, 1878 Jun 22 (Box 144, Folder 1486)
      - Music/ Suite parnassienne, [1912?] (Box 145, Folder 1487)
      - Music/ Suite théâtrale, n.d. (Box 146, Folder 1488)
      - Music/ Thérèse: draft, [ca. 1907] (Box 147, Folder 1489)
      - Music/ La Vierge, scene 1-2, 1878-80 (Box 148, Folder 1490)
      - Music/ La Vierge, scene 3, 1878-80 (Box 149, Folder 1491)
      - Music/ La Vierge, scene 4, 1878-80 (Box 150, Folder 1492)
    - Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix
      - Music/ Lieder ohne Worte, piano, op. 85, Nr. 5, 1847 May 6 (Box 151, Folder 1493)
      - Music/ Odipus in Kolonos, n.d. (Box 152, Folder 1494)
    - Milhaud, Darius
      - Music/ Mother Courage, [1959] (Box 153, Folder 1495)
    - Miller, Henry
      - Writings/ Tropic of Cancer, volume 1, [ca. 1930-32] (Box 154, Folder 1496)
      - Writings/ Tropic of Cancer, volume 2, [ca. 1930-32] (Box 155, Folder 1497)
      - Writings/ Tropic of Cancer, volume 3, [ca. 1930-32] (Box 156, Folder 1498)
      - Writings/ Tropic of Cancer, volume 4, [ca. 1930-32] (Box 157, Folder 1499)
    - Napoleon III, Emperor of the French
      - Other Papers/Album compiled by Baron Pierre de Bourgoing, 1741-1906, n.d. (Box 158, Folder 1500)
    - Offenbach, Jacques
      - Music/ Absence, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 1501)
      - Music/ Agnus Dei, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 1502)
      - Music/ L'amour chanteur, n.d. (Box 161, Folder 1503)
      - Music/ Apothicaire et perruquier, n.d. (Box 162, Folder 1504)
      - Music/ Après le jour, n.d. (Box 163, Folder 1505)
      - Music/ Ave Maria, n.d. (Box 164, Folder 1506)
      - Music/ Le barbier de Séville, 1852 Sep 25 (Box 165, Folder 1507)
      - Music/ Les contes d'Hoffmann, 1880, n.d. (Box 166, Folder 1508)
      - Music/ Le Décaméron: nos. 3-4, 6, and 8 (Box 167, Folder 1509)
      - Music/ Fantasio, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 1510)
      - Music/ La Foire Saint-Laurent, 1876, n.d. (Box 169, Folder 1511)
      - Music/ Hier la nuit d'été, n.d. (Box 170, Folder 1512)
      - Music/ La jolie parfumeuse, n.d. (Box 171, Folder 1513)
      - Music/ Le mariage de Figaro, 1852 Sep 15 (Box 172, Folder 1514)
      - Music/[ Nuit d'Espagne ?], n.d. (Box 173, Folder 1515)
      - Music/Opera and ballet music, 1859-[60?] (Box 174, Folder 1516)
      - Music/ Polka composée expressément pour Madame la comtesse de Chabrillan, n.d. (Box 175, Folder 1517)
      - Music/ Die Rheinnixen: short score, n.d. (Box 176, Folder 1518)
      - Music/ Die Rheinnixen: act 3, score, n.d. (Box 177, Folder 1519)
      - Music/ Le Roi Carotte, 1870, n.d. (Box 178, Folder 1520)
      - Music/Unidentified/Dance music for orchestra, n.d. (Box 179, Folder 1521)
      - Music/Unidentified/Sketches, drafts, and fragments (Box 180, Folder 1522)
    - Pacini, Giovanni
      - Music/ Bocca di paradiso, 1850 (Box 181, Folder 1523)
    - Poulenc, Francis
      - Music/ Les biches: short score, 1923 (Box 182, Folder 1524)
    - Puccini, Giacomo
      - Music/ La fanciulla del West: sketches, n.d. (Box 183, Folder 1525)
      - Music/ La fanciulla del West: fragment, n.d. (Box 184, Folder 1526)
    - Ravel, Maurice
      - Music/Arrangements/Mussorgsky, Modest Petrovich, Khovanshchina, [1913] (Box 185, Folder 1527)
    - Respighi, Ottorino
      - Music/ Antiche cantate d'amore. Quanta invidia mi fai, 1917, n.d. (Box 186, Folder 1528)
      - Music/Arrangements/Paisiello, La serva padrona: short score, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 1529)
      - Music/Arrangements/Paisiello, La serva padrona: score, 1920 Mar (Box 188, Folder 1530)
    - Rossini, Gioacchino
      - Music/ Cantata per Francesco I imperatore d'Austria, [1819] (Box 189, Folder 1531)
    - Roussel, Albert
      - Music/ Padmâvatî, n.d. (Box 190, Folder 1532)
      - Music/ Le testament de la tante Caroline, n.d. (Box 191, Folder 1533)
    - Saint-Saëns, Camille
      - Music/ The Promised Land: short score (Box 192, Folder 1534)
      - Music/ The Promised Land: score (Box 193, Folder 1535)
      - Music/ The Promised Land: Storage box of a former owner (Box 367)
      - Music/ Trio, piano, strings, no. 1, op. 18, F major, 1864 Oct (Box 194, Folder 1536)
    - Satie, Erik
      - Music/ Parade, [1917] (Box 195, Folder 1537)
    - Tennent, James Emerson, Sir
      - Other Papers/Album, 1822-64, n.d. (Box 196, Folder 1538)
    - Walton, William
      - Music/ As You Like It: score and drafts, [1936] (Box 197, Folder 1539)
      - Music/ The Battle of Britain: other sections, [1969] (Box 198, Folder 1540)
      - Music/ Christopher Columbus, [1942] (Box 199, Folder 1541)
      - Music/ Concerto, viola, orchestra: original version, [1929] (Box 200, Folder 1542)
      - Music/ Concerto, viola, orchestra: revised version, [1961] (Box 201, Folder 1543)
      - Music/ Concerto, violin, orchestra, 1943 (Box 202, Folder 1544)
      - Music/ Crown Imperial: score, [1937] (Box 203, Folder 1545)
      - Music/ Escape Me Never, [1934] (Box 204, Folder 1546)
      - Music/ The First Shoot, [1981] (Box 205, Folder 1547)
      - Music/ Gloria: short score and drafts, [1961] (Box 206, Folder 1548)
      - Music/ Hamlet, [1947] (Box 207, Folder 1549)
      - Music/ Henry V, [ca. 1943-44] (Box 208, Folder 1550)
      - Music/ Macbeth, [1941-42] (Box 209, Folder 1551)
      - Music/ Portsmouth Point: score, [1924-25] (Box 210, Folder 1552)
      - Music/ Portsmouth Point: score in the hand of Constant Lambert, [1926?] (Box 211, Folder 1553)
      - Music/ Quartet, strings, no. 1: incomplete score, 1920-22 (Box 212, Folder 1554)
      - Music/ The Quest: score in copyist's manuscript, [1943] (Box 213, Folder 1555)
      - Music/ Richard III, 1955 (Box 214, Folder 1556)
      - Music/ Scapino, [1940] (Box 215, Folder 1557)
      - Music/ Siesta, [1962] (Box 216, Folder 1558)
      - Music/ Sinfonia concertante, piano, orchestra, original version, [1927] (Box 217, Folder 1559)
      - Music/ Sinfonia concertante, piano, orchestra, revised version, [1943] (Box 218, Folder 1560)
      - Music/ Sonata, string orchestra, A minor, n.d. (Box 219, Folder 1561)
      - Music/ Symphony, no. 1, [1932-35] (Box 220, Folder 1562)
      - Music/ Troilus and Cressida, act I: score, [1947]-54 (Box 221, Folder 1563)
      - Music/ Troilus and Cressida, act II: score, [1947]-54 (Box 222, Folder 1564)
      - Music/ Troilus and Cressida, act III: score, [1947]-54 (Box 223, Folder 1565)
    - Whistler, Rex
      - Drawings/Illustrations for Jonathan Swift, Gulliver's Travels, 1929-1930 (Box 363)
      - Drawings/Illustrations for Jonathan Swift, Gulliver's Travels, 1929-1930 (Box 364)
      - Drawings/Illustrations for Jonathan Swift, Gulliver's Travels, 1929-1930 (Box 365)
      - Drawings/Illustrations for Jonathan Swift, Gulliver's Travels, 1929-1930 (Box 366)
    - Wolf-Ferrari, Ermanno
      - Music/ Gli amanti sposi, 1921, n.d. (Box 224, Folder 1566)
      - Music/ L'amore medico, 1910-12 (Box 225, Folder 1567)
      - Music/ Le baruffe chiozzotte, 1895 Mar 7 (Box 226, Folder 1568)
      - Music/ Cenerentola, 1898 (Box 227, Folder 1569)
      - Music/ Concertino, 1947, n.d. (Box 228, Folder 1570)
      - Music/ Concerto, violoncello, orchestra, op. 31, C major, n.d. (Box 229, Folder 1571)
      - Music/ La dama boba, n.d. (Box 230, Folder 1572)
      - Music/ Le donne curiose, n.d. (Box 231, Folder 1573)
      - Music/ I gioielli della Madonna, 1908, n.d. (Box 232, Folder 1574)
      - Music/ Das Himmelskleid, 1922, n.d. (Box 233, Folder 1575)
      - Music/ Idillio-concertino, [early 1930s] (Box 234, Folder 1576)
      - Music/ Irene, 1895, n.d. (Box 235, Folder 1577)
      - Music/ I quattro rusteghi, n.d. (Box 236, Folder 1578)
      - Music/ Sextet, violins, violas, violoncellos: score, 1895 Mar (Box 237, Folder 1579)
      - Music/ Sly, 1926, n.d. (Box 238, Folder 1580)
      - Music/ La Sulamite, 1898 Aug 18-27 (Box 239, Folder 1581)
      - Music/ Talitha Kumi, 1898 Oct 9-26 (Box 240, Folder 1582)
      - Music/ La vedova scaltra, 1929 Apr-Oct (Box 241, Folder 1583)
      - Music/ La vita nuova, 1901 Apr 24 (Box 242, Folder 1584)
      - Music/Unidentified/Instrumental and vocal works and libretti, 1945, n.d. (Box 243, Folder 1585)
      - Music/Unidentified/Opera, 1932 Jul (Box 244, Folder 1586)
  - Oversize Volumes
    - Baudelaire, Charles
      - Other Papers/"Messieurs de la lyre: les nuits de Monsieur Baudelaire", n.d. (Box 245, Folder 1587)
    - Cocteau, Jean
      - Writings/Poems ("Le Cap de Bonne Espérance," 1918) (Box 246, Folder 1588)
      - Writings/Poems ("Hommage à Bernard Buffet: gisant debout," 1955 Jul) (Box 247, Folder 1589)
    - Debussy, Claude
      - Music/ Ariettes oubliées. L'ombre des arbres, 1885 Jan 6 (Box 248, Folder 1590)
      - Music/ Fêtes galantes, 2. recueil. Colloque sentimental, n.d. (Box 249, Folder 1591)
      - Music/ Hymnis, n.d. (Box 250, Folder 1592)
    - Dvorák, Antonín
      - Music/ O sanctissima, 1890 May 28 (Box 251, Folder 1593)
    - Fauré, Gabriel
      - Music/Violin and piano music, 1884, n.d. (Box 252, Folder 1594)
    - Franck, César
      - Music/ Rébecca, 1881 Mar 17 (Box 253, Folder 1595)
    - German, Edward, Sir
      - Music/ Just So Song Book. Rolling Down to Rio, [1903] (Box 254, Folder 1596)
    - Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich
      - Music/ Finskaia fantaziia, 1910 Feb 20 (Box 255, Folder 1597)
    - Handel, George Frideric
      - Music/ Haec est regina virginum, [1707] (Box 256, Folder 1598-1598g)
      - Music/ Laudate pueri Dominum, HWV 237, [1707] (Box 257, Folder 1599-1599f)
      - Music/ Laudate pueri Dominum, HWV 237, [1707] (Box 257a, Folder 1599g-1599q)
      - Music/ Saeviat tellus inter rigores, [1707] (Box 258, Folder 1600-1600a)
      - Music/ Te decus virgineum, HWV 243, [1707] (Box 259, Folder 1601-1601f)
    - Lecocq, Charles
      - Music/ La fille de Madame Angot, n.d. (Box 260, Folder 1602)
    - Leoncavallo, Ruggiero
      - Music/ A chi la giarrettiera?, 1918 Jul (Box 261, Folder 1603)
      - Music/ Goffredo Mameli: Preludietto, act I, and Intermezzo in full score; drafts in short score; and notes, 1916, n.d. (Box 262, Folder 1604)
      - Music/ Goffredo Mameli: act II in full score, 1916, n.d. (Box 263, Folder 1605)
      - Music/ Maiá, act I: score, 1909-10 (Box 264, Folder 1606)
      - Music/ Maiá, act II: score, 1909-10 (Box 265, Folder 1607)
      - Music/ Maiá, act III: score, 1909-10 (Box 266, Folder 1608)
      - Music/ The Manicuring Girl, [ca. 1918-19] (Box 267, Folder 1609)
      - Music/ Pantins vivants, n.d. (Box 268, Folder 1610)
      - Music/ Pierrot au cinéma: score, [ca. 1919] (Box 269, Folder 1611)
    - Léopold I, King of the Belgians
      - Other Papers/Grant of the right to sit in the Royal Chapel at Windsor, 1816 May 25 (Box 270, Folder 1612)
    - Liszt, Franz
      - Music/ O du mein holder Abendstern, [ca. 1849] (Box 271, Folder 1613)
    - Louÿs, Pierre
      - Music/ Chanson des rois mages (Box 272, Folder 1614)
    - Mascagni, Pietro
      - Music/ Nerone, act I, 1933-34 (Box 273, Folder 1615)
      - Music/ Nerone, act II, 1933-34 (Box 274, Folder 1616)
      - Music/ Nerone, act III, 1933-34 (Box 275, Folder 1617)
    - Massenet, Jules
      - Music/ Chanson pour elle, [1897 or later] (Box 276, Folder 1618)
      - Music/ La terre promise, 1897-99 (Box 277, Folder 1619)
    - Milne, A. A. (Alan Alexander)
      - Writings/ When We Were Very Young / Six Drawings..., n.d. (Box 278, Folder 1620)
    - Offenbach, Jacques
      - Music/ Entrez, messieurs, mesdames, n.d. (Box 279, Folder 1621)
      - Music/ Les Géorgiennes, n.d. (Box 280, Folder 1622)
      - Music/ Whittington: no. 33, n.d. (Box 281, Folder 1623)
      - Music/Unidentified/Waltzes for orchestra, [1840?] (Box 282, Folder 1624)
      - Music/Unidentified/Waltzes for orchestra, n.d. (Box 283, Folder 1625)
    - Ponchielli, Amilcare
      - Music/ Omaggio a Donizetti, n.d. (Box 284, Folder 1626)
    - Proust, Marcel
      - Writings/ Le côté de Guermantes, 1919 (Box 285, Folder 1627)
      - Writings/ Sésame et les lys, n.d. (Box 286, Folder 1628)
    - Puccini, Giacomo
      - Music/ Madama Butterfly: "Addio, fiorito asil", [1904] (Box 287, Folder 1629)
      - Music/ Tosca, n.d. (Box 288, Folder 1630)
    - Wagner, Richard
      - Music/ Die Meistersinger von Nürnberg, 1866 Dec 24 (Box 289, Folder 1631)
    - Walton, William
      - Music/ Capriccio burlesco, 1968 Sep 5 (Box 290, Folder 1632)
      - Music/ Gloria: full score, n.d. (Box 291, Folder 1633)
      - Music/ Granada Preludes, Call Signs, and End Music, [1962] (Box 292, Folder 1634)
      - Music/ Improvisations on an Impromptu of Benjamin Britten, [1970] (Box 293, Folder 1635)
      - Music/ Johannesburg Festival Overture, 1956 May 31 (Box 294, Folder 1636)
      - Music/ Medley for Brass Band, [1981] (Box 295, Folder 1637)
      - Music/ Music for Children, [1940-41] (Box 296, Folder 1638)
      - Music/ The National Anthem, [1953] (Box 297, Folder 1639)
      - Music/ Orb and Sceptre, 1953 (Box 298, Folder 1640)
      - Music/ Partita, orchestra, [1957] (Box 299, Folder 1641)
      - Music/ Prologo e fantasia, [1981-82] (Box 300, Folder 1642)
      - Music/ Quartet, strings, no. 2, A minor, [1947] (Box 301, Folder 1643)
      - Music/ The Quest: score, partly in holograph, [1943] (Box 302, Folder 1644)
      - Music/ A Song for the Lord Mayor's Table: arrangement for voice and orchestra, [1970] (Box 303, Folder 1645)
      - Music/ The Spitfire Prelude and Fugue: original binder (Box 304, Folder 1646)
      - Music/ Symphony, no. 2: score, 1959-60 (Box 305, Folder 1647)
      - Music/ Troilus and Cressida: draft fragment and revisions, 1976, n.d. (Box 306, Folder 1648)
      - Music/ Variations on a Theme by Hindemith: drafts (Box 307, Folder 1649)
      - Music/ Variations on a Theme by Hindemith: score, 1963 Feb 6 (Box 308, Folder 1650)
      - Music/ Varii capricii: score, [1975-76] (Box 309, Folder 1651)
      - Music/ Varii capricii, no. 5, alternative version, n.d. (Box 310, Folder 1652)
    - Wolf-Ferrari, Ermanno
      - Music/ Cenerentola: original binding, 1898 (Box 311, Folder 1653)
      - Music/ Cenerentola: act I fragment, 1898 (Box 312, Folder 1654)
      - Music/ Fantasia, orchestra, 1895 May (Box 313, Folder 1655)
      - Music/ Quartet, strings, op. 23, E minor (Box 314, Folder 1656)
      - Music/ Quintet, violins, violas, violoncello, [early 1930s?] (Box 315, Folder 1657)
      - Music/Unidentified/Organ music: sketches, 1918, n.d. (Box 316, Folder 1658)
  - Folders Shelved Flat
    - Bantock, Granville, Sir
      - Music/ The Emperor, [1920?] (Box 317, Folder 1659)
      - Music/ The Garden of Bamboos, 1920 Feb 17 (Box 317, Folder 1660)
      - Music/ Longing, 1929 Apr 25 (Box 317, Folder 1661)
      - Music/ The Peach Flower, 1920 Mar 17 (Box 317, Folder 1662)
      - Music/ The Red Lotus, 1920 Apr 2 (Box 317, Folder 1663)
      - Music/ Reel (The Bobers of Brechin), 1917 Jun 9 (Box 317, Folder 1664)
      - Music/ Songs From the Chinese Poets, 1st-3rd ser. Adrift, 1918 Sep 12 (Box 317, Folder 1665)
      - Music/ Songs From the Chinese Poets, 1st-3rd ser. The Golden Nenuphar, 1918 Sep 13 (Box 317, Folder 1666)
      - Music/ Songs From the Chinese Poets, 1st-3rd ser. Yung-yang, 1918 Sep 14 (Box 317, Folder 1667)